getmyfilesnow.us 2013-07-21

# GetMyFilesNow - Download the files you want now

This privacy policy applies to the GetMyFilesNow extensions for Google Chrome, Firefox and for Internet Explorer (collectively and individually, "Extensions"), and is independent of any other application(s) you may be installing or using concurrently. The Extensions are provided and maintained by Linkular LLC, which may be referred to herein as "GetMyFilesNow," "We," "Us," or "Our" whether in uppercase, lowercase, or a combination. This Privacy Policy will also be applicable to additional browsers extensions, add-ons, or plug-ins, that are provided and maintained by Us. In the instance of the availability of any additional browser extensions, add-ons, or plug-ins, before it is or they are installed or added by you we will give you notice of the opportunity to install or add it or them, and give you the opportunity to agree and accept and install or add, or decline to install or add, it or them. Agreement may be by default. Because there may be more than one extension covered by this Privacy Policy the Extension and addition extensions may be referred to herein collectively and individually, as "Extensions." 

We want you to know that we care about your privacy and will never intentionally collect personally identifiable information or monitor usage on an individual level. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
Because of the rapidly evolving nature of the internet, computers, mobile technologies, and other technologies, in our attempts to make our user experience better, and for other aesthetic and business reasons, We may change, update and modify the Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a notice on our site at <http://www.getmyfilesnow.com/privacy/> , or in some other reasonable manner so You may always make yourself aware or be aware of what has changed. If any modification is unacceptable to You, You shall cease using the Extension and Services right away. If You do not cease using the Extensions and Services, You will be conclusively deemed to have accepted the change(s). Except as stated elsewhere, any amended Privacy Policy shall automatically be effective as soon as it is initially posted except if We states that We are is giving advance notice of any amended term to be effective on a date in the future. You agree that it is your responsibility to check the Privacy Policy and any guidelines periodically for changes. Except as posted by Us this Privacy Policy may not be otherwise amended, and no term may be waived by Us, except in a writing, hand signed by pen on paper (or as set forth below) by You and an authorized representative of Ours. For purposes of this provision, a "writing" does not include an email message, text, chat, or the like, sent from any device existing now or later developed and a signature does not include an electronic signature. 

**Information we collect during the installation and any susequent removal or uninstallation of the Extensions**  
The information we collect is for basic reporting purposes only, and consists of the following: 

  1. Date and time of installation
  2. Originating IP address and the user's country at time of installation/un-installation
  3. Partner ID at time of installation
  4. Extension version at time of installation
  5. A numeric identifier of the product that distributes the Extension (channel id)
  6. Media access control ("MAC") and operating system data

**Information we collect during Usage of the Extensions**  
We do not monitor the web pages you visit. When you perform a search, your search may be sent through our servers in order to optimize the search result. This will record the following information: 

  1. Date and time of search
  2. Originating IP address
  3. Partner / Channel ID of your Extension
  4. Extension version
  5. Search term(s)

In addition, your web browser will communicate to us information it gives to every web server that has placed one or more active cookies on your browser: ip address and browser user agent that contains information about your computer hardware and software attributes. 

**How we use the Information we collect**  
All information collected is reported by us on an aggregate basis. We may use this information to measure, for example: 

  1. the total number of Extension installs/uninstalls
  2. the number of active Extensions (to study browser trends, for example)
  3. the total number of DNS errors in order to measure growth patterns
  4. MAC and operating system data

**Information collected by Third Parties**  
Pages you visit when using the Extensions are provided by our partners. These partners can track the following: 

  1. Search term that was entered into the search box
  2. Originating IP address and the user's country or OS language setting
  3. Sponsored listings or other advertisements that you click on
  4. That the search request came from the extension and its associated revenue tag
  5. MAC and operating system data
  6. Partners might collect certain information

**No Spyware**  
The extensions do not collect personally identifiable information or monitor your surfing behavior. 

**Use of Cookies**  
When you are using the extensions, our content providers may set or access cookies on your computer. The cookies are used for the purpose of measuring referrals from our extensions on an aggregate basis and are not tied to your personal information, except for your IP Address, and as may be otherwise disclosed in the privacy policies of these providers. Many browsers offer users the option of declining or deleting cookies. If you do not wish to accept cookies, or you wish to delete cookies, please modify the settings in your browser. (A cookie is message given to a web browser by a web server. The message is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. There are many resources available on the internet that explain in greater detail what cookies are, what types of cookies exist, and what they do.) 

Also, please refer to the section above titled "Information collected by Third Parties" 

**Extensions Updates Automatically**  

The extensions communicate with our servers from time to time to check for available software updates such as bug fixes, patches, enhanced functions and new versions. By installing the extensions, **you agree to automatically request, receive and install updates without any additional notice.**

[The following within the brackets is for your information only, and is not a contractual agreement, including and notwithstanding anything stated or implied elsewhere 

**Extensions Uninstall**  

You can easily uninstall the extensions from your Google Chrome browser by selecting Settings > Extensions (or by selecting Chrome > Preferences > Extensions) > click Uninstall or Remove from Chrome or the trash can icon 

You can easily uninstall the extensions from your Firefox browser by selecting: Firefox > Preferences > General (tab) > Manage Add-ons > Remove 

Extension Deactivation 

You can easily hide or deactivate the extensions in Google Chrome by selecting Settings > Extensions(or by selecting Chrome > Preferences > Extensions) , and then unselecting the checkbox for the the specific extension. 

You can easily hide or deactivate the extensions in Firefox by selecting Firefox > __ Preferences > General (tab) > Manage Add-ons > Disable] 

**Children's Privacy**  
We recognize the privacy interests of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests. The Extensions are not intended for children under the age of 13. We do not target the Extensions or our Services to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE, PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THE EXTENSION AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER. IF WE LEARNS THAT PERSONALLY-IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION OF PERSONS LESS THAN 13 YEARS OF AGE HAS BEEN COLLECTED ON OR THROUGH AN EXTENSION, WE WILL TAKE THE APPROPRIATE STEPS TO DELETE THIS INFORMATION. 

IF YOU ARE THE PARENT OR LEGAL GUARDIAN OF A CHILD UNDER 13 WHO HAS BECOME AN EXTENSION USER SUBSCRIBER, THEN PLEASE CONTACT GETMYFILESNOW AT SUPPORT@COOLLINKS.US TO HAVE THAT CHILD'S ACCOUNT TERMINATED AND INFORMATION DELETED. 

THE FOLLOWING ARE SOME RESOURCES THAT MAY HELP PARENTS AND LEGAL GUARDIANS IN MONITORING AND LIMITING YOUR CHILDREN'S ACCESS TO CERTAIN TYPES OF MATERIAL ON THE INTERNET. WHILE WE DOES NO ENDORSE THESE SITES, SERVICES, OR PRODUCTS, AND DISCLAIMS ANY RESPONSIBILITY IN CONNECTION WITH THEM, WE PROVIDE INFORMATION ABOUT THEM AS A PUBLIC SERVICE. 

  1. [OnGuard Online](http://onguardonline.gov/socialnetworking.html) , maintained by the Federal Trade Commission. 
  2. [WiredSafety](http://www.wiredsafety.org/)
  3. [Netsmartz.org](http://netsmartz.org/)
  4. [The Child Safety Network](http://www.csn.org/index.jsp)
  5. [Control Kids](http://www.controlkids.com/)
  6. [Cyber Sitter](http://www.solidoak.com/)
  7. [Net Nanny](http://www.netnanny.com/)

**INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE**  
We do not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

  * We provide the information to trusted business affiliates who work with us or on our behalf under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help us communicate with you about offers from us and our marketing partners. 
  * We have a parent's permission to share the information if the user is a child under age 13. Parents have the option of allowing GetMyFilesNow to collect and use their child's information without consenting to GetMyFilesNow sharing of this information with people and companies who may use this information for their own purposes. 
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected illegal activities, fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Use, or as may otherwise be required by law or regulation. 
  * We transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company. 

**Notice to European Users**  
The information You enter on or through An Extension or otherwise provide to us may be transferred outside of the European Union to the United States of America, which does not offer an equivalent level of protection to that required in the European Union. In particular, You are advised that the United States of America uses a sectoral model of privacy protection that relies on a mix of legislation, governmental regulation, and self-regulation. Article 26 of the European Union's Data Protection Directive (Directive 95/46/EC, 1995 O.J. (L 281) 31) allows for transfer of personal data from the European Union to a third country if the individual has unambiguously given his consent to the transfer of personal information, regardless of the third country's level of protection. By agreeing to the terms of use and this privacy policy, You consent to the transfer of all such information to the United States of America, which may not offer an equivalent level of protection to that required in the European Union and to the processing of that information by us on our servers located in the United States of America as described in this Privacy Policy. 

**Questions and Suggestions**  
If you have questions or suggestions, please send us a note at _support@coollinks.us_. 

Effective Date: May 29th 2013
